yixe.com 2007-12-10

# yiXe! - Privacy Policy

We at Yixe Media LLC. understand that you value your privacy and we strive to respect that privacy when you are using our services. This Privacy Policy describes what information we gather from you, how we use that information and what we do to protect it. By using the Yixe Media website, you are expressly consenting to the information handling practices described in this policy.

## Information We Collect From You

When you sign up with Yixe Media, you establish a password-protected personal account for ordering ringtones, graphics, games and other items and services. During the account creating process and/or to place an order, we request contact information (such as name, a valid email address, cell phone number and address) and certain billing information (such as a credit card number and expiration date.)

In addition, we may occasionally request information from users via online membership profiles, surveys or contests. Participation in these profiles, surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and mailing address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level).

Once you create an account, we keep track of your interactions with us, including but not limited to your site activity, order history, payment history and correspondence with us.

Our website may provide you with the opportunity to send emails to your friends, family members or relatives. For this feature of our site to work, we need to collect the email address(es) of those to whom you send messages. The email addresses we collect in this context are not used for any other purpose other than to send your request. We will only resend an email to these email addresses at your request.

Our websites’ servers collect and retain technical information regarding visits to our website such as the IP address assigned to the computer visiting the site, the type of browser used by a visitor and the operating system running the user’s connections to the service. This data is not linked to your personal account. It is used in the aggregate to analyze the ways in which our site is used, and how we can improve the user experience, and may be shared, in the aggregate, with third parties such as advertisers.

## Information Relating to Children

You must be at least thirteen (13) years of age to use the Yixe Media Services. Any person who provides their information to Yixe Media through the account registration page for new customers or any other part of the Yixe Media site represents to Yixe Media that they are 13 years of age or older. If you are between 13 and 17, you agree that you received parental permission both to complete the registration process and to download content to your cell phone. Yixe Media is in no way directed at children under 13 years of age. We will not knowingly collect personal information of children under 13 years of age, and if we learn that we have inadvertently collected such information, we will promptly delete it.

## How We Use Your Information

Yixe Media uses your personal information in the following general ways: To provide you with the Yixe Media services, to allow for your identification and authentication onto the Yixe Media website, to contact you for billing and administrative functions, and for internal research and reporting purposes. We also use the information provided by you in surveys for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of the Yixe Media service.

We may also send you site and service announcement updates with important information about the service through the email address or cell phone number you provide. We may also notify you about special promotions available through trusted partners. You can opt-out of receiving these promotional emails, but not service related messages, at any time either through a link in emails we send you, or by visiting http://static.Yixe Media.com/unsub/unsub.html

## Viewing and Updating Your Account Information

If you want to update your contact information or change credit cards, you can do so by visiting the Account section of our web site. You must be signed in to access Your Account. You can also make changes to some of your privacy preferences, including your e-mail preferences, by going to Your Account section.

## Cookies

Cookies are pieces of information that your browser receives from Web sites and stores on your computer's hard drive. Information in cookies includes preferences you select while visiting a particular Web site. For example, by storing cookies on your hard drive, you'll return to a specific Web site with the same settings you used on a previous visit. Yixe Media never saves information such as your credit card number on cookies. We do require cookies in order to manage and individual visits the Yixe Media site. Certain cookies are also used to determine how you were referred to the Yixe Media site as well as your browsing and buying activities, in order that we can determine the success of any particular online marketing campaign. If you have cookies turned off, you will not be able to access the Yixe Media service. If you enter our pages from the site of one of Yixe Media’s partners, our system will recognize the path you have taken. Yixe Media advertises on such partners' sites or we've entered into a promotional partnership with them. We track the number of visitors that these partners send us to see the success of our online marketing or promotional campaign. These partners will not know your personal information, unless you have given it to them separately or consent to give it to them through us. 

## Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties

We do not sell, rent or share your personal information with non-affiliated third parties for direct marketing purposes or otherwise, without your consent. We do, however, share your information with trusted third party contractors who provide services for us. For example, we may provide your personal information to phone companies in order to ensure that we can properly bill for our services. These third party contractors are prohibited from using the information we provide for purposes other than performing services for us.

We may disclose your information to third parties when we reasonably believe we are obligated to do so by law, and in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual prohibited activities, including without limitation, fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person and violations of Yixe Media terms of use.

Finally, we may transfer information, including any personally identifiable information, to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets or other corporate change regarding our website.

## Third Party Sites Appearing on the Yixe Media Site

The Yixe Media website contains links to and advertisements for sites operated by third parties whose policies regarding the handling of personal information may differ from ours. While we endeavor to associate only with reputable sites, Yixe Media cannot be responsible for the information handling practices of these other sites.

## Protecting your information

Yixe Media makes reasonable efforts safeguard your personal information. However, due to the open communication nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and the site, and the site and you, will be free from unauthorized access by third parties. Your use of the site and disclosure of your personal information is at your own risk. 

If Yixe Media learns of a security breach through which sensitive personal information may have been compromised, we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using this web site, or providing personal information to us through any means, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of this site.

## International Visitors

Yixe Media is hosted in the United States and is intended only for United States visitors. At this time, Yixe Media’s services are not available to overseas visitors.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy 

This policy is effective as of April 24,2006 As we update and expand our services, we may make changes to this policy. If the changes result in materially less protection for your personal information than that provided in this policy, we will make reasonable efforts to contact you and obtain your consent to the changes before using information that we have previously collected.

## Contact Information 

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@Yixe Media.com](mailto:support@Yixe%20Media.com)
